Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
[Between Love and Frost]
[بين الحب والصقيع]
[Episode 13]
[الحلقة 13]
[Director's Office]
[مكتب المدير]
Mr. Gu,
السيد جو،
Mr. Liu didn't name specifically
السيد ليو لم يذكر اسمًا محددًا
Gu Tongpei as the successor.
جو تونغبي خليفةً.
Seems he's handing you an opening.
يبدو أنه يقدم لك فرصة.
Why not seize it
لماذا لا نغتنمها
and take the position?
وخذ المنصب؟
But what they want is money.
لكن ما يريدونه هو المال.
I'm making Gu Tongpei the successor
أنا أجعل Gu Tongpei الخليفة
to make him let his guard down.
لجعله يخفض حذره.
After all, the old man just died.
بعد كل هذا، الرجل العجوز مات للتو.
If I overthrew the successor he chose,
إذا أطاحت بالخليفة الذي اختاره،
it'd be tough to convince the public.
سيكون من الصعب إقناع الجمهور.
Gu Tongpei is consumed by vengeance.
غو تونغبي يستهلكه الانتقام.
He'll accomplish nothing.
لن يحقق شيئا.
Later, when I step in as emergency governor,
وفي وقت لاحق، عندما توليت منصب حاكم الطوارئ،
it makes my authority justifiable.
إنه يجعل سلطتي مبررة.
Your judgment is spot-on!
حكمك في محله!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
Take the gold from my safe
خذ الذهب من خزانتي
and distribute it to veteran officers.
وتوزيعها على الضباط المخضرمين.
My succession depends on their backing.
خلافتي تعتمد على دعمهم.
And rush
واندفع
the search for Chu Minghui.
البحث عن تشو مينغ هوي.
I need her alive.
أحتاجها على قيد الحياة.
Yes.
نعم.
Tongpei,
تونجبي,
sorry for your loss.
آسف على خسارتك.
You and Chu Minghui killed Father together.
أنت وتشو مينغ هوي قتلتم الأب معًا.
I'll absolutely uncover the truth.
سأكشف الحقيقة بالتأكيد.
None of you will escape.
لن ينجو أحد منكم.
You've misunderstood me,
لقد أساءت فهمي
Tongpei.
تونجبي.
I was also deceived by her.
لقد خدعتني أيضًا.
In the past,
في الماضي،
I was such a fool.
لقد كنت أحمقًا جدًا.
Only after Father's death did I truly see
ولم أره حقًا إلا بعد وفاة والدي.
you two are the ones
أنتما الاثنان
I hold dearest in this life.
أعز ما عندي في هذه الحياة.
From this day forward,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
you're my only family
أنت عائلتي الوحيدة
in this world.
في هذا العالم.
Tongpei,
تونجبي,
we must stand together.
يجب علينا أن نقف معًا.
Chu Minghui murdered Father
قتل تشو مينغوي الأب
in such a brutal way.
بهذه الطريقة الوحشية.
We'll make her pay.
سوف نجعلها تدفع الثمن.
During his lifetime,
خلال حياته،
Father cherished you above all else.
لقد كان والدك يعتز بك فوق كل شيء.
You must
يجب عليك أن
personally avenge him.
انتقم له شخصيا.
Otherwise, he'll never rest in peace.
وإلا فلن يرتاح بسلام أبدًا.
Gu Tongpei,
قو تونجبي,
go ahead and torment Chu Minghui.
اذهب إلى الأمام وعذب تشو مينغ هوي.
This is all for Father.
كل هذا من أجل الأب.
Here you are.
تفضل.
Are you
أنت
sending a maid to stay here?
إرسال خادمة للبقاء هنا؟
The lodging fees are charged per person.
يتم فرض رسوم الإقامة على كل شخص.
Rest assured, I'll keep my lips sealed.
اطمئن، سأبقي شفتي مغلقة.
Hurry inside now.
اسرع إلى الداخل الآن.
Wait here.
انتظر هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
All men
جميع الرجال
are scums.
إنهم حثالة.
Does it hurt?
هل يؤلمك؟
My father must have been
لا بد أن والدي كان
in much more pain when he died.
كان في ألم أكبر بكثير عندما مات.
Why did you kill him?
لماذا قتلته؟
Why did you torture him
لماذا عذبته؟
in such a cruel way?
بهذه الطريقة القاسية؟
Was this your own scheme,
هل كان هذا مخططك الخاص؟
or a plot hatched with Gu Tongce?
أم مؤامرة مع غو تونغسي؟
Spill it.
انسكبه.
I want the whole truth.
أريد الحقيقة كاملة.
If you're seeking revenge, kill me.
إذا كنت تبحث عن الانتقام، اقتلني.
The rich torture people
الأغنياء يعذبون الناس
in a truly unique way.
بطريقة فريدة حقا.
Chilling just to hear about them.
من المثير للرعب أن أسمع عنهم.
Stay out of their spat.
ابق بعيدًا عن جدالهم.
Getting mixed up in this
التورط في هذا
will only bring you trouble.
لن يجلب لك سوى المتاعب.
Chu Minghui,
تشو مينغوي,
things won't end like this.
لن تنتهي الأمور بهذه الطريقة.
[Memorial Tablet for Gu Rongchong]
[لوحة تذكارية لغو رونغتشونغ]
Bow before my father.
انحني أمام والدي.
In your dreams!
في أحلامك!
Chu Minghui,
تشو مينغوي,
I gave you chance after chance,
لقد أعطيتك الفرصة تلو الفرصة،
yet you lied to me again and again,
ومع ذلك كذبت علي مرارا وتكرارا،
trampling my sincerity under your feet!
دوس صدقي تحت قدميك!
You even murdered my father cruelly!
لقد قتلت والدي بوحشية!
I really wish I could cut you to pieces!
أتمنى حقًا أن أتمكن من تقطيعك إلى قطع!
That was my father!
هذا كان والدي!
Even if he'd done something wrong,
حتى لو كان قد فعل شيئا خاطئا،
he gave me life and raised me!
لقد أعطاني الحياة وربياني!
How could you kill him like that?
كيف يمكنك قتله بهذه الطريقة؟
Just tell me why,
فقط أخبرني لماذا
and I'll grant you a merciful death.
وسأمنحك موتة رحيمة.
Nothing left to say.
لم يبق شيء ليقال.
I deceived you.
لقد خدعتك.
I owed you.
لقد كنت مدين لك.
Now I repay you.
الآن سأرد لك الجميل.
You may kill yourself,
قد تقتل نفسك،
but don't dirty my father's memorial hall.
لكن لا تلوث قاعة تذكارية والدي.
Now that you hate me this much,
الآن بعد أن أصبحت تكرهني بهذا القدر،
why not finish me off?
لماذا لا تقضي علي؟
Chu Minghui,
تشو مينغوي,
without my permission,
بدون إذني،
don't even think about dying.
لا تفكر حتى بالموت.
Deal with the injury you caused.
تعامل مع الإصابة التي تسببت بها.
♪Love is an abyss one cannot escape♪
♪الحب هو الهاوية التي لا يمكن الهروب منها♪
♪The more I doubt, the more I fear♪
كلما زاد شكي، زاد خوفي
♪Sparks of hatred ignite within the heart♪
♪تشتعل شرارات الكراهية في القلب♪
How could you hit her?
كيف يمكنك ضربها؟
This is
هذا هو
my mother's necklace.
قلادة أمي.
♪I guard myself over and over again♪
♪أحمي نفسي مرارا وتكرارا♪
She left it to the one I treasure most.
لقد تركتها للشخص الذي أعزّه كثيرًا.
♪I hesitate in every word and every moment♪
♪أتردد في كل كلمة وفي كل لحظة♪
♪I feign, struggle♪
♪أتظاهر، أكافح♪
♪Flee, and break♪
♪اهرب وانكسر♪
♪The endless shackle of darkness♪
♪قيد الظلام الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪Let love come♪
♪دع الحب يأتي♪
♪No more worries♪
♪لا مزيد من القلق♪
As long as you're here,
طالما أنك هنا،
even if I suffer grave injuries,
حتى لو كنت أعاني من إصابات خطيرة،
I'll surely heal quickly.
سأشفى سريعا بالتأكيد.
♪Crush it♪
♪سحقها♪
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
take good care of yourself.
اعتني بنفسك جيدا.
♪Keep it to yourself♪
♪احتفظ بها لنفسك♪
Never let yourself be hurt easily again.
لا تسمح لنفسك بأن تُجرح بسهولة مرة أخرى.
♪Let the hatred go♪
♪اترك الكراهية تذهب♪
You deceived me.
لقد خدعتني.
♪Don't dwell♪
♪لا تتوقف♪
♪Only when flowers wither will scars form♪
♪فقط عندما تذبل الزهور تتشكل الندوب♪
♪Let love and hate scatter with the wind♪
♪دع الحب والكراهية يتناثران مع الريح♪
Keep this in mind.
ضع هذا في الاعتبار.
This is what you owe me.
هذا ما تدينني به.
Your life belongs to me.
حياتك ملكي.
Do you think my wounds and agony
هل تعتقد أن جروحي وألمي
can be mended easily?
هل يمكن اصلاحها بسهولة؟
♪Let myself be free♪
♪أسمح لنفسي أن أكون حرا♪
Miss Chu.
السيدة تشو.
Keep an eye on her.
ابقي عينك عليها.
Don't let her die.
لا تدعها تموت.
Miss Chu,
الآنسة تشو،
please don't go head-to-head with him.
من فضلك لا تتواجه معه وجها لوجه.
Do you two have to be like this?
هل يجب أن تكونا مثل هذا؟
You're both such good people.
أنتم الاثنان شخصان طيبان.
Don't torture each other.
لا تعذبوا بعضكم البعض.
I'm not a good person.
أنا لست شخصا جيدا.
Perhaps only when I vanish,
ربما فقط عندما أختفي،
can all this come to an end.
هل يمكن أن ينتهي كل هذا؟
Miss Chu,
الآنسة تشو،
I don't know what happened
لا أعلم ماذا حدث
between you two.
بينكما.
But only by staying alive,
ولكن فقط بالبقاء على قيد الحياة،
can you resolve misunderstandings.
هل تستطيع حل سوء التفاهم؟
Yet resolving them
ولكن حلها
would thrust him deeper into anguish.
من شأنه أن يدفعه إلى مزيد من الألم.
If he knows our feud,
إذا كان يعرف عداوتنا،
it'll bring him endless torment.
سيجلب له عذابًا لا نهاية له.
Die,
ال،
I'd like some hot noodle soup.
أريد بعض حساء المعكرونة الساخنة.
Could you make me a bowl?
هل يمكنك أن تصنع لي وعاء؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Just leave it here.
فقط اتركه هنا.
Go and return soon.
اذهب و عد قريبا.
Die.
ال.
Sir.
سيد.
Keep her wounds dry
حافظ على جروحها جافة
these two days.
هذين اليومين.
Be vigilant!
كن يقظا!
Ensure that she won't get a fever.
تأكد من أنها لن تصاب بالحمى.
Understood.
مفهومة.
Sir,
سيد،
please stop torturing each other.
من فضلكم توقفوا عن تعذيب بعضكم البعض.
Go prepare some nourishing food for her.
اذهب لإعداد بعض الأطعمة المغذية لها.
Yes.
نعم.
♪Love is an abyss one cannot escape♪
♪الحب هو الهاوية التي لا يمكن الهروب منها♪
♪The more I doubt, the more I fear♪
كلما زاد شكي، زاد خوفي
♪Sparks of hatred ignite within the heart♪
♪تشتعل شرارات الكراهية في القلب♪
♪The more I struggle, the hoarser my voice becomes♪
كلما كافحت أكثر، أصبح صوتي أكثر خشونة
♪I guard myself over and over again♪
♪أحمي نفسي مرارا وتكرارا♪
♪I hesitate in every word and every moment♪
♪أتردد في كل كلمة وفي كل لحظة♪
♪I feign, struggle♪
♪أتظاهر، أكافح♪
♪Flee, and break♪
♪اهرب وانكسر♪
♪The endless shackle of darkness♪
♪قيد الظلام الذي لا نهاية له♪
♪Let the hatred go♪
♪اترك الكراهية تذهب♪
♪Don't dwell♪
♪لا تتوقف♪
♪Only when flowers wither will scars form♪
♪فقط عندما تذبل الزهور تتشكل الندوب♪
♪Let love and hate scatter with the wind♪
♪دع الحب والكراهية يتناثران مع الريح♪
♪Let myself be free♪
♪أسمح لنفسي أن أكون حرا♪